{
    "subject": "resource/Century_Milstead",
    "predicate": "property/college",
    "object": "resource/Wabash_College",
    "human_readable": "Century Milstead attended Wabash College.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9864932894706726,
            "question": "Did Century Milstead study at Wabash College?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9842146635055542,
            "question": "Is Century Milstead a graduate of Wabash College?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9787287712097168,
            "question": "Is Wabash College a place where Century Milstead studied?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9620948433876038,
            "question": "Name the college that Century Milstead attended."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9387267827987671,
            "question": "Where did Century Milstead attend college?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.894388735294342,
            "question": "To which college did Century Milstead go?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8893336057662964,
            "question": "What is the name of the college Century Milstead attended?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8564184308052063,
            "question": "What college did Century Milstead go to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7172321081161499,
            "question": "What educational institution was Century Milstead associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6997377276420593,
            "question": "What is the name of the college Century Milstead graduated from?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Century Milstead attended Wabash College.",
            "html": "dbpedia_196_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What educational institution was Century Milstead associated with?",
            "html": "dbpedia_196_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What college did Century Milstead go to?",
            "html": "dbpedia_196_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the college Century Milstead attended?",
            "html": "dbpedia_196_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_196_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_196_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_196_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_196_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_196_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_196_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_196_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_196_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_196_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_196_62.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the required format:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents provide information about Century Allen Milstead's football career, including his time at Wabash College. The text mentions that he played tackle play first at Wabash and later at Yale (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_196/re-ranker-msmarco/59.txt), which supports the triple that Century Milstead attended Wabash College."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Century Allen Milstead played college football at Wabash College, which supports the statement that he attended Wabash College."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}